Hello.
こんにちは
It's so cute.
めちゃくちゃ可愛いですね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Hey, that's amazing.
ねえ、すごい
That's good.
いいっすね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
I'm going to be a little nervous,
ちょっとボッキーしちゃいますよ、
Something.
なんか
It smells good.
いい匂いするんで
That's not the case.
そんなことないです
Please give me a little introduction.
ちょっと紹介をね、してもらってね
I had him come today, and I actually saw it.
今日来てもらったんですけど、 実は見たんですよね、
Video.
映像を
Oh, yes.
ああ、はい
If you see it.
見ちゃったら
I want to meet you.
会いたいなと思って
It's so erotic.
すげえエロいんで
thank you.
ありがとうございます
I got out.
抜けました
Is it true?
本当ですか?
That's how they react.
そういう反応してくるんですね
I thought it was going to turn me off.
ドン引きすんのかと思ったの
No, I don't pull it at all.
いやいや、全然引かないです
Can I ask you a few questions?
ちょっといろいろ聞いてもいいですか?
What do you usually do now?
今は普段何してるんですか?
I usually work as a high school teacher.
普段は高校の教師をしています
Are you a teacher?
先生なの?
Yes, that's right.
はい、そうです
Not at all.
全然そんなことないです
What subjects do you teach?
教科は何を教えてるんですか?
I'm teaching the plaintiff.
原告を教えてます
That's right.
そうなんですね
Are you smart?
頭よくて?
Not at all.
全然そんなことないです
Do you feel like you went to university as usual today?
今日も普通に大学出ていった感じですか?
that's right.
そうです
It's like going to university, studying, and getting a job.
大学出て勉強とって就職って感じ
Are you smart at university too?
大学も頭いいんですか?
No, that's not true.
いや、そんなことないですよ
How big is it?
一体大ですか?
Nippon Sport Science University?
日本体育大学?
No, not at all.
いやいや、全然違います
It's the Japanese language.
国語だもんね
How big is it?
どこ大なんですか?
Chuo University.
中央大学です
Aren't you really smart?
めちゃくちゃ頭いいじゃないですか?
Not at all.
全然そんなことないです
Why did you decide to become a Japanese language teacher?
なんで国語の先生なのと思ったんですか?
I realized that I loved reading books, and my high school teacher was very helpful to me.
本読み好きだなと思ったのと、 高校の先生にとてもお世話にな
That's why I wanted to aim for it too.
った ので、 私も目指しにたいなと思ってなりました
It's wonderful.
素敵ですね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Isn't it difficult for school teachers?
学校の先生大変じゃないですか?
I agree.
そうですね
I think the hardest part is having to work a lot of overtime.
残業が多いのが 一番大変かなと思います
Ah, there are a lot of them.
あ、 やっぱ多いんだ
You say it often.
よく言いますよね
You have a lot of work to do, so what do you find difficult?
仕事も多くて、 どんなことが大変だったりしますか?
Because I have club activities, I have to work on Saturdays and Sundays,
部活とかがあると、 土日も出勤しなくちゃいけなくなるので、
It's tough, isn't it?
大変ですね
Oh, what club activities are you teaching?
あ、何の部活を教えてるんですか?
I am an advisor to the drama club.
演劇部を顧問しています
It's tough, isn't it?
大変なんですね
I agree.
そうですね
The drama club?
演劇部か
Are there any male students?
男子生徒います?
I'm here.
います
Have you been confessed to anything?
何 か告白されたりとかしてないですか?
Not at the moment.
今のところはないですね
If I had a teacher like this, I would get an erection during class.
こんな先生いたら、 授業中勃起しますよ
That's tough.
それは大変ですね
Do any teachers have erections during class?
授 業中勃起してる先生はいないですか?
No, I won't watch it.
いや、見ないです
Don't you see it?
見ない?
I don't watch it.
見ないんですよ
I was working during class.
俺 授業中仕事ってましたもん
That's tough.
それは大変ですね
hard?
大変?
I'm sure you'll find it.
絶対見つかってますよ
What kind of classes are you teaching now?
今どんな授業をしてるんですか?
Currently, I am teaching Natsume Soseki.
今は、夏目漱石を教えてます
He uses a brother called Goro.
ゴロという兄弟を使ってますね
Please tell me too.
ちょっと俺も教えて
Tell me too.
俺にも教えて
Speaking of Natsume Soseki, today...
夏目漱石といえば、 今日、
Do you know a man who likes Natsume Soseki?
夏 目漱石が好きな男を 知 ってるんですか?
Thank you.
どうも
I really like Natsume Soseki.
夏目漱石、すごい好きです
Is that so?
そうなんですか?
I would like to have such a beautiful teacher teach me.
こんな美人な先生に教えてもらいますね
That's outrageous.
とんでもないです
I envy the students.
学生たちって羨ましいですね
At this time, he was 6 years old and a grandfather.
こちらの時、6歳おじいちゃんだったのに
To the teacher.
先生にね
That will give the students an erection.
それは生徒の勃起しますもんね
Really.
本当に
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
He's a shameful man.
恥ずかしい男なんでね
If you're a teacher, it's tiring.
先生だったら 疲れますよね
I agree.
そうですね
Don't you read it in terms of physical theory?
結構、肉体論で読むんじゃないですか?
No, not at all.
いや、全然
That's not the case.
そんなことないです
Is it true?
本当ですか?
I feel like I have quite a few.
結構、持ってる気がするけど
That's a really good job.
すごい良い仕事ですね
So, it's huge.
で、でかいっすね
That's not the case.
そんなことないですね
How many cups is it?
何カップくらいですか?
It's a G cup.
Gカップね
Isn't it huge?
でかいじゃないですか?
dislike.
嫌い
Isn't there a style?
スタイルとかないですか?
No, nothing.
いや、何もないです
Really?
本当に?
If I had a teacher with good style, I would definitely have paid for it.
スタイル良い先生いたら 絶対お金が出たですよ
Don't you think about that?
それこれ考えないですか?
I think about it sometimes.
たまに考えます
Are you thinking about it?
考えちゃう?
Isn't it really good?
めちゃくちゃ良いじゃないですか?
You know what a really nice butt, right?
めちゃくちゃ良いお尻知ってるじゃないですか?
No, it's embarrassing.
いや、恥ずかしいです
Did you wear pants like this that you like?
こんなちょっと好き好きなパンツ入ってたんすか?
That's disgusting.
いやらしいな
You have really beautiful skin.
めちゃくちゃ綺麗な肌してるんですね
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいですか?
I've definitely been watching more than usual.
普段からずっと 絶対もっと見られてます
No.
ダメです
Did you flush it?
流したなんですか?
No.
ダメです
why?
なんで?
Is the bottom okay?
下も大丈夫ですか?
No, no.
いや、ダメです
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Really?
本当に?
Sensei, you have surprisingly good eyes.
先生、意外と好き目ですよね
That's not the case.
そんなことないです
そんな こと ない です
Please stop for a moment.
ちょっとやめてください
It's a little.
少しです
Is it no good?
ダメですか?
No.
ダメです
No?
ダメ?
No.
ダメです
You don't want to look away when you talk, do you?
喋るとよけ見たくないじゃないですか?
I'm an embarrassing teacher.
恥ずかしい先生です
a
あ
Please don't look too closely.
ん まり見ないでください
That's amazing.
すごいですね
Do you usually wear brands like this?
普段からこういうブランなんすか?
Please don't look at it too much.
あ ん まり 見 ないでください
If it was black or purple, it would be see-through.
黒とか紫だったら透けちゃいますね
I think this is still very visible to the students.
これでも生徒にはめっちゃ見られてると思います
I'll give you a massage.
マッサージをやる
why?
なんで?
When I massaged it with this, the teacher also said,
これかけてマッサージしたら 先生もね、
I think it's relaxing.
リラックスできると思うんですよ
What's changing?
何が変わってますか?
Don't you feel hot?
体熱くなってこないですか?
What happened?
どうしました?
どう しました?
I'm more surprised than before.
さっきより びっくりしてますよ
Did you like it?
気に入りました?
This massage oil.
このマッサージオイル
Ah, it's cold.
あ、寒い
I work among teachers.
先生の中で仕事をやってますね
I can still try to hide it.
まだ隠そうとできるんですけどね
I wonder if the teacher is mentally strong enough to do it alone?
先生だけやって精神力強いのかな?
I'll give you a drink
飲んであげます
mosquito?
か?
My body is also getting thinner and thinner.
体 もどんどん痩れてきてますよ
Teacher, even Pumpy is becoming transparent.
先生、パンピーも 透けてきちゃってますね
It would be a waste to hide it.
隠したらもったいないですよ
Such a beautiful place.
こんな綺麗なところ
I'm really used to it
すっごい慣れてます
hey.
ね
Does it feel this good?
こんな 気持ちいいですか?
Can I watch it?
見ちゃっていいですか?
The teacher is starting to lose his patience, right?
先生はもう我慢できなくなってきてるでしょ?
Oh, it's so completely visible.
ああ、すっごい丸見えですよ、
gentlemen.
先生
Your butt is still in disarray,
お 尻のままでしっかり乱れちゃってますよ、
this.
これ
I can't open everything.
すべて開けないですね
Isn't it shaky?
ふるふるじゃないですか?
Does it feel good like this?
こんな気持ちいいですか?
It's easy to swallow.
簡単に飲み込んじゃいますね
I'm starting to become a monster because of my lack of patience.
我慢だるだるで怪物になってきますね
Should I let my gentle breasts do the work for me?
優しいおっぱいで仕事をやってもらおうかな?
Do it yourself like this.
自分でこうやって
Should I ask such a beautiful teacher to do it for me?
こんな美人の先生にやってもらうかな?
Sensei, you're starting to lose your patience, aren't you?
先生、我慢できなくなってきたんじゃないですか?
Wow, it's getting hot.
すごい、暑くなってきた
Is it getting hot?
暑くなってきちゃったの?
Actually, this is a stimulant.
実はこれ、覚醒剤なんですよ
Please take a break.
休憩してください